Guide to the Time Inc. Time-Life News Service Records 1935-1987 MS 3009-RG 14
New-York Historical Society
- Series I. Chief of Correspondent Files, 1935-1987; 60.5 Linear feet in 60 record cartons, 1 flat box
  - Subseries I.C. Chief of Correspondents Richard Duncan Files, 1980-1987; 1.7 Linear feet in 4 record cartons
    - European Symposium, 1982-1983 (Offsite-box 3186, Folder 51)
    - Evaluations, 1984 (Offsite-box 3186, Folder 52)
    - Fischer, Dean, 1985 (Offsite-box 3186, Folder 53)
    - Foreign Minister of Lebanon, 1983 (Offsite-box 3186, Folder 54)
    - Foreign Minister of Nigeria, 1984 (Offsite-box 3186, Folder 55)
    - Foreign Policy Association, 1983 (Offsite-box 3186, Folder 56)
    - Friendly, Alfred: Fellow Program, 1986 (Offsite-box 3186, Folder 57)
    - Grunwald: San Francisco Meeting: 1985 Sept. (Offsite-box 3186, Folder 58)
    - Hart, Gary: Lunch, 1983 (Offsite-box 3186, Folder 59)
    - Hemisphere Club: Receipts, 1982 (Offsite-box 3186, Folder 60)
    - Hill, Ernie: Miami Conference, 1982 (Offsite-box 3186, Folder 61)
    - Hollings, Ernest: Lunch, 1983 (Offsite-box 3186, Folder 62)
    - Hong Kong, undated (Offsite-box 3187, Folder 1)
    - Hunt, James, 1984 (Offsite-box 3187, Folder 2)
    - Inauguration: 1981 and 1985, 1980-1984 (Offsite-box 3187, Folder 3-4)
    - Invitation Types, 1985 (Offsite-box 3187, Folder 5)
    - Japan Issue, 1983-1984 (Offsite-box 3187, Folder 6)
    - Japanese Edition, 1983 (Offsite-box 3187, Folder 7)
    - Joint Chiefs of Staff, 1983-1984 (Offsite-box 3187, Folder 8)
    - Jordan, Hamilton, 1983 (Offsite-box 3187, Folder 9)
    - Kirk, Paul: Lunch, 1986 (Offsite-box 3187, Folder 10)
    - Koch, Ed, 1986 (Offsite-box 3187, Folder 11)
    - Korb, Lawrence, 1984 (Offsite-box 3187, Folder 12)
    - Korean Dinner: 1984 March 2 (Offsite-box 3187, Folder 13)
    - Lerner, Steve, 1985 (Offsite-box 3187, Folder 14)
    - Linden, Eugene, undated (Offsite-box 3187, Folder 15)
    - London: Art Show: 1983 September (Offsite-box 3187, Folder 16)
    - London: Trip: May 6-9, 1980 (Offsite-box 3187, Folder 17)
    - Matheson, Scott, 1983 (Offsite-box 3187, Folder 18)
    - McGovern, George: Lunch: May 24, 1984 (Offsite-box 3187, Folder 19)
    - Memo, 1982 (Offsite-box 3187, Folder 20)
    - Mexico City: Party, 1983 (Offsite-box 3187, Folder 21)
    - Mexico News Tour, 1983 (Offsite-box 3187, Folder 22)
    - Middle East Meeting, 1982 (Offsite-box 3187, Folder 23)
    - Midwest: Political Trip: 1982 Oct. (Offsite-box 3187, Folder 24)
    - Miscellaneous, 1983-1984 (Offsite-box 3187, Folder 25)
    - Moscow Visas, 1986 (Offsite-box 3187, Folder 26)
    - Moscow Visas [RESTRICTED], 1981-1986 (Offsite-box R46)
    - M.O.Y., undated (Offsite-box 3187, Folder 27)
    - Muller and Stacks Trip: 1986 Feb. (Offsite-box 3187, Folder 28)
    - Murdoch, Rupert: Lunch, 1982 (Offsite-box 3187, Folder 29)
    - NASA: Beggs, James, 1985 (Offsite-box 3187, Folder 30)
    - New York, Budapest, Rome, and Geneva, 1986 (Offsite-box 3187, Folder 31)
    - News Tour, 1985 (Offsite-box 3187, Folder 32)
    - Novak, Michael: Sept. 11, 1982 (Offsite-box 3187, Folder 33)
    - Oltmans vs. Time, 1984-1985 (Offsite-box 3187, Folder 34)
    - Ortega, Daniel, 1983 (Offsite-box 3187, Folder 35)
    - Overseas Press Club Dinner, 1980-1983 (Offsite-box 3187, Folder 36)
    - Owen, David, 1983 (Offsite-box 3187, Folder 37)
    - Pentagon Panel: Press Meeting, 1984 (Offsite-box 3187, Folder 38)
    - Peres, Shimon: Coffee: Nov. 11, 1982 (Offsite-box 3187, Folder 39)
    - Peres, Shimon: Luncheon: Oct. 11, 1984 (Offsite-box 3187, Folder 40)
    - Political Meeting: New York: 1987 January 19, undated (Offsite-box 3187, Folder 41)
    - Quinn, Thomas, 1984 (Offsite-box 3187, Folder 42)
    - Reilly, William: Lunch: Sept. 9, 1986 (Offsite-box 3187, Folder 43)
    - Rosenne, Meir; Coffee, 1983 (Offsite-box 3187, Folder 44)
    - Rowney, Edward: Coffee, 1984 (Offsite-box 3187, Folder 45)
    - Russians: Lunch with AP: Dec. 14, undated (Offsite-box 3187, Folder 46)
    - Saar, John, undated (Offsite-box 3187, Folder 47)
    - Shultz, George, undated (Offsite-box 3187, Folder 48)
    - Sidey, Hugh: Anniversary, 1985 (Offsite-box 3187, Folder 49)
    - Singapore, 1983 (Offsite-box 3187, Folder 50)
    - Snelling, Richard, 1982 (Offsite-box 3187, Folder 51)
    - Teeter, Bob, 1984 (Offsite-box 3187, Folder 52)
    - Toronto Trip, 1983 (Offsite-box 3187, Folder 53)
    - TV Project, 1981-1982 (Offsite-box 3187, Folder 54)
    - Ueberroth, Peter, 1983 (Offsite-box 3187, Folder 55)
    - United States-Soviet Relations Symposium: 1984 November (Offsite-box 3187, Folder 56)
    - White, Teddy, 1983-1984 (Offsite-box 3187, Folder 57-58)
    - White, Teddy [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Offsite-box R46)
    - Wilson, O'Patrick, 1983 (Offsite-box 3187, Folder 59)
    - Zamyatin, Leonid: Soviet Invitation, 1983 (Offsite-box 3188, Folder 1)
    - Zia-ul-Haq, Muhammad, 1982 (Offsite-box 3188, Folder 2)
  - Subseries I.D. General Files, 1944-1987; 46.95 Linear feet in 46 record cartons, 1 flat box
    The General Files cover the period of 1944 through 1987 and contain materials created by a variety of chiefs of correspondents at the Time-Life News Service. Several sets of General Files were found. It is unclear who grouped files from different chiefs together, if an administrator within the Time-Life News Service or the Time Inc. Archives was responsible. The separate sets have been grouped together alphabetically as one series.
    Folder titles include a mix of names, places, and subjects. While the Bureau files subseries and Staff Files series contain folders with titles and materials similar to those found in this subseries, the materials have not been interfiled. The main reason that these materials have remained separate is because they were found stored and arranged separately from one another.
    Contained in this subseries are payroll forms, employment applications, resumes and CVs, clippings, invitations, guests lists, dispatches, translated articles, benefits summary sheets, annual reports, awards ceremony pamphlets, requisition forms, biographical summaries, press releases, conflict of interest and employment policies, department heads lists, error reports, evaluation guidelines, meeting transcripts, photos, negatives, contact lists, prospectuses, list of Time Inc. board members, news bureau surveys and results, distribution lists, financial statements and reports, seating lists and charts, vacation schedules, query sheets, lists of bureau staff, immigration and visa forms, reports on newstour participants, background research reports for newstours, reports attitudes toward Time, and memoranda and correspondence. The memoranda and correspondence within this series discusses budgets, travel plans, hiring, salaries, contact information, raises, research, bureau operations and updates, costs, article corrections and comments, staffing changes, stringers, job candidates, job responsibilities, meetings, conflicts of interest, masthead changes and acknowledgments, interview requests, job enquiries, meetings, invitations, censorship, story and project proposals, policies, lawsuits, contracts, shipping of supplies, correspondent assignments, newstour proposals, updates on newstours, schedules, and bureau finances.
    - Abrams, Eliot, 1985 (Offsite-box 3141, Folder 1)
    - Accreditation: United States, 1960-1961 (Offsite-box 3141, Folder 2)
    - Adenauer, Konrad: Memoires, 1963 (Offsite-box 3141, Folder 3)
    - Africa, 1962-1969 (Offsite-box 3141, Folder 4)
    - Agnew, Spiro, 1968-1972 (Offsite-box 3141, Folder 5)
    - Ahrold, Robbin, 1969-1973 (Offsite-box 3141, Folder 6)
    - Ajemian, Bob, 1976 (Offsite-box 3141, Folder 7)
    - Alexander, Roy: Farewells, 1966 (Offsite-box 3141, Folder 8)
    - Allen, Lew, 1979 (Offsite-box 3141, Folder 9)
    - Alumni Society, undated (Offsite-box 3141, Folder 10)
    - American Corporations Abroad, 1966 (Offsite-box 3141, Folder 11)
    - American Power Pack for Peace: Islands of Light, undated (Offsite-box 3141, Folder 12)
    - Anderson, John, 1979 (Offsite-box 3141, Folder 13)
    - Andreotti, Guilo: Dinner, 1979 (Offsite-box 3141, Folder 14)
    - Angelo, Bonnie: Party, 1978 (Offsite-box 3141, Folder 15)
    - Annual Report, 1975-1976 (Offsite-box 3141, Folder 16)
    - ANPA Reception, 1965 (Offsite-box 3141, Folder 17)
    - Applicants: Pending [EMPTY], undated (Offsite-box 3141, Folder 18)
    - Arbatov, Georgi, 1971 (Offsite-box 3141, Folder 19)
    - Archives: Photographs, undated (Offsite-box 3141, Folder 20)
    - Ashkinaze, Carol, 1976 (Offsite-box 3141, Folder 21)
    - Associated Press, 1962-1975 (Offsite-box 3141, Folder 22-24)
    - Associated Press [RESTRICTED], 1969 (Offsite-box R44)
    - Atlanta, 1962-1985 (Offsite-box 3141, Folder 25-28)
    - Atlanta: Bureau Move, 1975 (Offsite-box 3141, Folder 29)
    - Atlanta: Party, 1967-1977 (Offsite-box 3141, Folder 30)
    - Atlanta: Personnel, 1962-1972 (Offsite-box 3141, Folder 31)
    - Atlanta: Personnel [RESTRICTED], 1965-1972 (Offsite-box R44)
    - Audio Project, 1969 (Offsite-box 3141, Folder 32)
    - Auer, Bernhard: Correspondence, 1965 (Offsite-box 3141, Folder 33)
    - Awards, 1976 (Offsite-box 3141, Folder 34)
    - B: Miscellaneous [EMPTY], undated (Offsite-box 3141, Folder 35)
    - Back of the Book, 1974-1975 (Offsite-box 3141, Folder 36)
    - Back of the Book Study, 1974-1975 (Offsite-box 3141, Folder 37)
    - Back of the Book Suggestions, 1976 (Offsite-box 3141, Folder 38)
    - Baires, 1972-1977 (Offsite-box 3141, Folder 39-40)
    - Baker, Bobby: Investigations, 1962-1964 (Offsite-box 3141, Folder 41)
    - Baker, Howard: Lunch, 1979 (Offsite-box 3141, Folder 42)
    - Baker, Jim: Lunch, 1976 (Offsite-box 3141, Folder 43)
    - Barcelo, Carlos Romero, 1979 (Offsite-box 3141, Folder 44)
    - Bardach, Ann: Lawsuit, 1984-1985 (Offsite-box 3141, Folder 45)
    - Bardach, Ann: Lawsuit [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Offsite-box R44)
    - Bauer, David Calvin, 1987 (Offsite-box 3141, Folder 46)
    - Beglund, Bob: Coffee, 1979 (Offsite-box 3141, Folder 47)
    - Beirut, 1973-1976 (Offsite-box 3141, Folder 48-49)
    - Beirut, 1962-1976 (Offsite-box 3142, Folder 1-2)
    - Beirut [RESTRICTED], 1963 (Offsite-box R44)
    - Beirut: Intrabank, 1967 (Offsite-box 3142, Folder 3)
    - Beirut: Personnel, 1954-1973 (Offsite-box 3142, Folder 4-5)
    - Belgrade, 1973 (Offsite-box 3142, Folder 6)
    - Bell, James, 1956-1985 (Offsite-box 3142, Folder 7-8)
    - Bell, James [RESTRICTED], 1970, 1977-1980 (Offsite-box R44)
    - Bennett, Walter, 1958 (Offsite-box 3142, Folder 9)
    - Bennett, Walter [RESTRICTED], 1965 (Offsite-box R44)
    - Berkeley, 1970 (Offsite-box 3142, Folder 10)
    - Berlin, 1962, 1977-1978 (Offsite-box 3142, Folder 11-13)
    - Bernstein, Richard, 1975-1982 (Offsite-box 3142, Folder 14)
    - Bernstein, Richard [RESTRICTED], 1979-1982 (Offsite-box R44)
    - Bhuto, 1973 (Offsite-box 3142, Folder 15)
    - Bicentennial Issue, 1962-1976 (Offsite-box 3142, Folder 16)
    - Birnbaum, Jesse, 1977 (Offsite-box 3142, Folder 17)
    - "Black" [African-American] Issue, 1970 (Offsite-box 3142, Folder 18)
    - Blaylock, Bill, 1973-1983 (Offsite-box 3142, Folder 19-20)
    - Blaylock, Bill [RESTRICTED], 1979-1983 (Offsite-box R44)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 1981 (Offsite-box 3142, Folder 21)
    - Bolte, Gisela: Visa: New York Bureau, 1969, 1977-1978 (Offsite-box 3142, Folder 22)
    - Bolte, Gisela: Visa: New York Bureau [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Offsite-box R44)
    - Bonn, 1972-1978 (Offsite-box 3142, Folder 23-24)
    - Bonn [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Offsite-box R44)
    - Bonn: Stringers, 1956-1968 (Offsite-box 3142, Folder 25)
    - Book Division, 1961-1970 (Offsite-box 3142, Folder 26)
    - Book Order Requests, 1973-1978 (Offsite-box 3142, Folder 27)
    - Boston, 1965-1985 (Offsite-box 3142, Folder 28-29)
    - Boston: Personnel, 1961-1968, 1979 (Offsite-box 3142, Folder 30)
    - Boston: Personnel [RESTRICTED], 1972 (Offsite-box R44)
    - Boston: Stringers, 1962-1966, 1984 (Offsite-box 3142, Folder 31)
    - Box Score, 1977 (Offsite-box 3142, Folder 32)
    - Boyle, John: Memoranda, 1960 (Offsite-box 3143, Folder 1)
    - Boyle, John: Memoranda: Mailing Instructions, undated (Offsite-box 3143, Folder 2)
    - Boyle, John: Memoranda: Time Editorial, undated (Offsite-box 3143, Folder 3)
    - Bradford, Ned: Little, Brown and Co., 1973 (Offsite-box 3143, Folder 4)
    - Brandt, Willy, 1971 (Offsite-box 3143, Folder 5)
    - Brandt, Willy [RESTRICTED], undated (Offsite-box R44)
    - Brezhnev, Leonid L., 1977 (Offsite-box 3143, Folder 6)
    - Bright Young Men Project, 1961-1964 (Offsite-box 3143, Folder 7-9)
    - Broadcasting: News Director Tour, 1965, undated (Offsite-box 3143, Folder 10)
    - Broadcasting: TV and Radio, 1959-1962, 1968-1970 (Offsite-box 3143, Folder 11)
    - Brown, Jerry, undated (Offsite-box 3143, Folder 12)
    - Brussels, 1969-1976 (Offsite-box 3143, Folder 13-14)
    - Budget, 1974-1979 (Offsite-box 3143, Folder 15-16)
    - Buenos Aires, 1970-1981 (Offsite-box 3143, Folder 17)
    - Buenos Aires [RESTRICTED], 1970 (Offsite-box R44)
    - Bureau Chiefs, 1972-1975 (Offsite-box 3143, Folder 18)
    - Bureau Chiefs' Meeting, 1960, 1986 (Offsite-box 3143, Folder 19-21)
    - Bureau Christmas Bonuses, 1970-1971 (Offsite-box 3143, Folder 22)
    - Bureau Contact List, 1976 (Offsite-box 3143, Folder 23)
    - Bureau Contact List: Foreign Staff, 1958, 1965-1968 (Offsite-box 3143, Folder 24)
    - Bureau Correspondence, 1977 (Offsite-box 3143, Folder 25)
    - Burg, Joseph, 1979 (Offsite-box 3143, Folder 26)
    - Burton, Sandra: Boston Bureau Chief Party, 1973 (Offsite-box 3143, Folder 27-28)
    - Bush, George: Coffee, 1979 (Offsite-box 3143, Folder 29)
    - Business/Economy Section, 1972-1974 (Offsite-box 3143, Folder 30)
    - Byline Summary, 1971 (Offsite-box 3143, Folder 31)
    - Bylines, 1982 (Offsite-box 3143, Folder 32)
    - C: Miscellaneous, 1961-1968 (Offsite-box 3143, Folder 33)
    - C: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 1969 (Offsite-box R44)
    - Cable Costs, 1960-1966 (Offsite-box 3143, Folder 34-35)
    - Cable Desk, 1967-1971 (Offsite-box 3143, Folder 36)
    - Cable Desk: Computer Proposal, 1966-1970 (Offsite-box 3143, Folder 37)
    - Cable Desk: Personnel, 1963-1971 (Offsite-box 3144, Folder 1)
    - Cable Desk: Personnel [RESTRICTED], 1963-1964 (Offsite-box R44)
    - Cable Tolls and Wordage, 1960-1965 (Offsite-box 3144, Folder 2-3)
    - Cabot Prize, 1971 (Offsite-box 3144, Folder 4)
    - Cadieux, Marcel and Dick O'Hagen: Lunch, 1973 (Offsite-box 3144, Folder 5)
    - Cairo, 1974-1978 (Offsite-box 3144, Folder 6)
    - Cambodia, 1967-1968 (Offsite-box 3144, Folder 7)
    - Cameron, Denis, 1974 (Offsite-box 3144, Folder 8)
    - Canada, 1959-1976 (Offsite-box 3144, Folder 9-14)
    - Canadian Royal Commission on Foreign Magazine, 1959-1965 (Offsite-box 3144, Folder 15-16)
    - Cannes Festival, 1973 (Offsite-box 3144, Folder 17)
    - Capital Appropriations, 1963-1967 (Offsite-box 3144, Folder 18)
    - Caramalis, Greece, 1977 (Offsite-box 3144, Folder 19)
    - Carter, Jimmy, 1976 (Offsite-box 3144, Folder 20)
    - Carter, Jimmy: Inauguration, 1976-1977 (Offsite-box 3144, Folder 21)
    - Casey, William: Lunch: September 11, 1986 (Offsite-box 3144, Folder 22)
    - Cate, Ben: Correspondence, 1972-1975 (Offsite-box 3144, Folder 23)
    - Cate, Ben: Correspondence: Miscellaneous, 1972-1975 (Offsite-box 3144, Folder 24-25)
    - Cave, Ray, 1975-1978 (Offsite-box 3144, Folder 26)
    - Censorship Problems, 1964-1970 (Offsite-box 3144, Folder 27)
    - Center for Inter-american Relations, 1977 (Offsite-box 3144, Folder 28)
    - Century Club, 1985 (Offsite-box 3144, Folder 29)
    - Chen, Percy, 1976 (Offsite-box 3144, Folder 30)
    - Chicago, 1972-1978 (Offsite-box 3144, Folder 31)
    - Chicago: Cate, Ben: Welcoming Party: 1975 September, 1975, 1984-1987 (Offsite-box 3144, Folder 32-33)
    - Chicago: Party: November 23, 1971 (Offsite-box 3144, Folder 34-35)
    - Chicago: Personnel, 1961-1971, 1985 (Offsite-box 3144, Folder 36)
    - Chicago: Personnel [RESTRICTED], 1965-1971, 1979 (Offsite-box R44)
    - Chicago: Trip, 1961-1971, 1985 (Offsite-box 3144, Folder 37)
    - China, 1962-1978 (Offsite-box 3145, Folder 1-9)
    - China [RESTRICTED], undated (Offsite-box R44)
    - China: Lunch, 1976 (Offsite-box 3145, Folder 10)
    - China: May-Lee Industries, 1972-1973 (Offsite-box 3145, Folder 11)
    - China: Peking Trip, 1955-1963 (Offsite-box 3145, Folder 12-13)
    - China: Special File, 1958-1959 (Offsite-box 3145, Folder 14-15)
    - China: Visas, 1965 (Offsite-box 3145, Folder 16)
    - China: Visas [RESTRICTED], 1965 (Offsite-box R44)
    - China, Red, 1956-1957 (Offsite-box 3145, Folder 17-18)
    - China, Red [RESTRICTED], 1957 (Offsite-box R44)
    - Chou en Lai's Trip, 1963 (Offsite-box 3145, Folder 19)
    - Christmas Party, 1986 (Offsite-box 3145, Folder 20)
    - Church, Frank: April 30, 1979 (Offsite-box 3145, Folder 21)
    - CIA, 1973-1980 (Offsite-box 3145, Folder 22-24)
    - CIA [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Offsite-box R44)
    - Civil Defense, 1958-1963 (Offsite-box 3145, Folder 25)
    - Civil Rights, undated (Offsite-box 3145, Folder 26)
    - Clark, Champ, 1976 (Offsite-box 3146, Folder 1)
    - Clark, Marsh: Medical Forms [RESTRICTED], undated (Offsite-box R44)
    - Clips, 1975 (Offsite-box 3146, Folder 2)
    - Clubs, 1970 (Offsite-box 3146, Folder 3)
    - Clurman, Richard: Journalism Project, 1965 (Offsite-box 3146, Folder 4-6)
    - Clurman, Richard: What is a Time Query, 1958 (Offsite-box 3146, Folder 7)
    - Clurman, Richard: Winfrey, Carey: Project, 1970 (Offsite-box 3146, Folder 8)
    - Coca Cola: P and C, 1979 (Offsite-box 3146, Folder 9)
    - Colby, William, 1977 (Offsite-box 3146, Folder 10)
    - Color Projects, 1977 (Offsite-box 3146, Folder 11)
    - Columbia University, 1963 (Offsite-box 3146, Folder 12)
    - Comak Cable Communications: Cohn, Hugh: Houston, 1982 (Offsite-box 3146, Folder 13)
    - Communications Department, 1964-1971 (Offsite-box 3146, Folder 14-15)
    - Communication Department [RESTRICTED], 1969 (Offsite-box R44)
    - Communism, 1964 (Offsite-box 3146, Folder 16)
    - Computerization, 1972-1973 (Offsite-box 3146, Folder 17)
    - Confidential Memos, 1960-1969 (Offsite-box 3146, Folder 18)
    - Conflict of Interest, 1977-1986 (Offsite-box 3146, Folder 19)
    - Conflicts of Interest: Time Inc.'s Policy, 1961-1965, 1971-1974 (Offsite-box 3146, Folder 20)
    - Congo: 1960 July and 1961 Sept., 1960-1961 (Offsite-box 3146, Folder 21)
    - Congressional Dinner, 1974-1975 (Offsite-box 3146, Folder 22-23)
    - Constantine II, 1973 (Offsite-box 3146, Folder 24)
    - Contact Lists: Montreal and New York Bureaus, 1973 (Offsite-box 3146, Folder 25)
    - Copyright Law, 1977 (Offsite-box 3146, Folder 26)
    - Corporate Offices, 1973-1974 (Offsite-box 3146, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence: All Correspondent Memos, 1964 (Offsite-box 3146, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence: Chron File, 1978 (Offsite-box 3146, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence: Chron File [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Offsite-box R44)
    - Correspondence: Clurman, Richard, 1960-1966, 1974 (Offsite-box 3146, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence: Filing Foreign Messages Memos, 1957-1962, 1968 (Offsite-box 3146, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence: Follow Ups, 1965 (Offsite-box 3146, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence: Follow Ups: Correspondents with Letter Writers, 1965 (Offsite-box 3146, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence: Foreign Bureau Communications, 1950-1955 (Offsite-box 3146, Folder 34)
    - Correspondence: Journalism Project, 1965 (Offsite-box 3147, Folder 1-6)
    - Correspondence: Miscellaneous, 1960-1961, 1972-1976 (Offsite-box 3147, Folder 7)
    - Correspondents: Error Reports, 1976 (Offsite-box 3147, Folder 8)
    - Correspondents: Fund, 1982-1984 (Offsite-box 3147, Folder 9)
    - Correspondents: General Fund, 1978-1979 (Offsite-box 3147, Folder 10)
    - Correspondents: Language Proficiencies, 1954 (Offsite-box 3147, Folder 11)
    - Corruption, 1963 (Offsite-box 3147, Folder 12)
    - Cost of Living, 1972-1978 (Offsite-box 3147, Folder 13-16)
    - Costs: Foreign Bureaus: 1951-1952, 1949-1952 (Offsite-box 3147, Folder 17)
    - Council on Foreign Relations, 1977, undated (Offsite-box 3147, Folder 18-19)
      Folder 19 is empty.
    - Council on Foreign Relations, Inc., 1973-1975 (Offsite-box 3147, Folder 20)
    - The Councilor, 1975 (Offsite-box 3147, Folder 21)
    - CRT, 1976-1975 (Offsite-box 3147, Folder 22-23)
    - Cuba, 1961-1963, 1977 (Offsite-box 3147, Folder 24-25)
    - Cuba Study, 1975 (Offsite-box 3147, Folder 26-27)
    - Cuban Picture Caption, 1975 (Offsite-box 3147, Folder 28)
    - Cuomo, Mario: Lunch, 1984-1985 (Offsite-box 3147, Folder 29-30)
    - Cyprus: First Week, 1974 (Offsite-box 3148, Folder 1)
    - D: Miscellaneous, 1962-1971 (Offsite-box 3148, Folder 2)
    - Darden, Norman, 1976-1977 (Offsite-box 3148, Folder 3)
    - Davis, Angela, 1971-1972 (Offsite-box 3148, Folder 4)
    - Democrats, 1960 (Offsite-box 3148, Folder 5)
    - Department of Defense, 1961 (Offsite-box 3148, Folder 6)
    - Department Heads, 1976-1977 (Offsite-box 3148, Folder 7)
    - Desk Assignment Division, 1962 (Offsite-box 3148, Folder 8)
    - Desk Reports, 1969-1971 (Offsite-box 3148, Folder 9-13)
    - Desk Reports and Forms, 1969-1970 (Offsite-box 3148, Folder 14-15)
    - Detroit, 1972-1978 (Offsite-box 3148, Folder 16-17)
    - Detroit: Personnel [RESTRICTED], 1962-1966 (Offsite-box R44)
    - Detroit: Party, 1978 (Offsite-box 3148, Folder 18)
    - Detroit: Personnel, 1963-1968 (Offsite-box 3148, Folder 19)
    - Detroit vs. Time, 1961 (Offsite-box 3148, Folder 20)
    - Developmental Journalism, 1976 (Offsite-box 3148, Folder 21)
    - DeVoss, David, 1969-1985 (Offsite-box 3148, Folder 22-24)
    - DeVoss, David [RESTRICTED], 1978-1985 (Offsite-box R44)
    - DiFatta,Peter, 1969-1971 (Offsite-box 3148, Folder 25)
    - DiFatta, Peter [RESTRICTED], 1969-1971 (Offsite-box R44)
    - Dispatches: Update on America, 1985 (Offsite-box 3148, Folder 26)
    - Doerner, William, 1978-1980 (Offsite-box 3148, Folder 27)
    - Doerner, William [RESTRICTED], 1978-1982 (Offsite-box R44)
    - Dole, Robert, 1977 (Offsite-box 3148, Folder 28)
    - Domestic Bureaus, 1972 (Offsite-box 3148, Folder 29)
    - Domestic Bureaus Chiefs, 1977 (Offsite-box 3148, Folder 30-31)
    - Domestic Bureaus Chiefs Meeting, 1986 (Offsite-box 3148, Folder 32)
    - Domestic Staff List, 1975 (Offsite-box 3148, Folder 33-34)
    - Donovan, Hedley, undated (Offsite-box 3148, Folder 35)
    - Donovan, Hedley: China, 1978-1979 (Offsite-box 3148, Folder 36)
    - Donovan, Hedley: Trip, 1976-1979 (Offsite-box 3148, Folder 37)
    - Donovan, Hedley and Dick Duncan: Trip, 1978-1979 (Offsite-box 3148, Folder 38)
    - Donovan, Hedley and Dick Duncan: Trip, 1978-1979 (Offsite-box 3149, Folder 1)
    - Donovan, Hedley and Dick Duncan: Trip: 1979 January [RESTRICTED], 1978-1979 (Offsite-box R44)
    - Donovan, Hedley and Henry: Party, 1979 (Offsite-box 3149, Folder 2)
    - Douglas-Hume, Charles, 1983 (Offsite-box 3149, Folder 3)
    - Dowd, Maureen, 1982 (Offsite-box 3149, Folder 4)
    - Dowell, Bill: Contract [RESTRICTED], 1987 (Offsite-box R44)
    - Draft Joke Correspondence, undated (Offsite-box 3149, Folder 5)
    - Drozdiak, Bill, 1976-1979 (Offsite-box 3149, Folder 6-7)
    - Drozdiak, Bill [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Offsite-box R44)
    - Duke Fellowship, 1982-1984 (Offsite-box 3149, Folder 8)
    - Duncan, Dick: Correspondence, 1969-1984 (Offsite-box 3149, Folder 9-13)
    - Duncan, Dick: Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1973, 1983 (Offsite-box R44)
    - Duncan, Dick: Correspondence: Miscellaneous, 1975-1978 (Offsite-box 3149, Folder 14)
    - Duncan, Dick: Correspondence: Personal, 19775-1977 (Offsite-box 3149, Folder 15)